http://www.pearlsforteengirls.com/privacy-policy

Corporate Partners
Privacy PolicyPEARLS for Teen Girls recognizes that your privacy is important, and that you have the right to know how we treat the information you provide to us through this Web Site. If you have questions about privacy that this Privacy Policy does not answer below, please contact us via the Web Site or at PEARLS for Teen Girls, 1805 N. Martin Luther King Dr., Milwaukee, WI 53212.Information GatheredExcept as described herein, PEARLS for Teen Girls does not gather or track any personal information about you unless you specifically elect to share that information with us through the Web Site. In certain areas of the Web Site, we may ask for contact information (your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number) when you ask us to send you periodic newsletters, fundraising initiatives and other information. When we do gather this and any other information, we do so to enable us to further the purposes of PEARLS for Teen Girls and to continually improve your experience with PEARLS for Teen Girls and our Web Site.Use and Distribution of InformationIt is PEARLS for Teen Girls’ policy to comply with all applicable laws and regulations relating to its use of confidential information to the extent such laws apply to it and its operations. In addition to any other uses, we may use your information to communicate with you regarding the use of the Web Site, to inform you of changes to the Web Site or events, fundraising and other initiatives that we think you may wish to know about, to analyze and maintain the Web Site, and to evaluate where Web Site users link to and from. Using information in this way enables us to better serve you, and to present a Web Site that best suits your needs.Cookies“Cookies” are small bits of information that are stored by your browser onto your hard drive as you visit web pages. Like many other web sites, we may use these tools for purposes such as monitoring the traffic flow of visitors from other sites. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may be able to change your browser settings to prevent this. If you reject cookies from our Web Site, some parts of the Web Site may not work properly and may not be available. Contact your Internet service provider for more information.SecurityExcept where otherwise noted, PEARLS for Teen Girls does not use encryption technology to protect the information that we collect from you. If any information you send is misdirected or intercepted, it can be read by others. Accordingly, do not send confidential information or specific personal information to us through the Web Site or email.Corrections or Updates in Your Information/Opt-Out PolicyIf you have questions or concerns about the use of information on this Web Site, please bring it to our attention. While we will investigate any concern that you may have regarding the collection and use of information on the Web Site, the sole remedy to objections over that collection and use remains for you to discontinue using the Web Site. Whenever the Web Site offers you the opportunity to provide information, you have the option to withhold that information. If you do so, certain offerings of PEARLS for Teen Girls (e.g., newsletters) may not be available to you. You may request that we delete your information from our records by contacting us via the Web Site, at the address listed in the introductory paragraph above, or through any "opt-out" features contained in any electronic communications.
Get the latest news, invites and updates from PEARLS for Teen Girls.
First Name
Last Name
Email Address
Sign Up
Thank you!
Back to Top
PEARLS for Teen Girls, 1805 North Martin Luther King Jr. Drive, Milwaukee, WI, 532124142657555info@pearlsforteengirls.com
Contact Us
Staff
Events
Give to PEARLS
Enroll in PEARLS
Careers
© 2020 PEARLS for Teen Girls, Inc. All rights reserved. Locally crafted by PEARLS for Teen Girls is proud to be a United Way sponsored agency!Privacy Policy
|
Site Map
